Lukasz Pietraszek

UI/Front-end developer

PERSONAL SUMMARY

UI/Front-end developer with proven track-record over five years in creating clean, accessible and user-friendly responsive websites. Self motivated and adaptable, independent minded, with a keen eye for detail. Experienced in working with Hybris CMS and Agile methodologies

Specialities: HTML5, CSS3, Web Design/Development, RWD, Usability, Web Standards, Axure RP, Hybris CMS

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI Developer

August 2013 — present

Portaltech Reply, London // www.portaltech.co.uk

Developing and integrating front-end with Hybris[y] CMS for number of e-commerce websites using HTML5, CSS3, Less/SASS, Bootstrap 3, jQuery and Grunt.js Clients: Phones4U, Monsoon Accessorize, OFFICE, BAT, Delhaize, P&O Ferries, Costco

Web Designer/Developer

Aug 2006 — present

Looca Design, London // looca.co.uk

Looca Design is my own freelance design company. For several years I have been creating website portfolios, brochures, and business cards. My clients list include established online businesses, international charities and independent artists. I work closely with my clients to create designs that are clean, crisp and effective.

Front-end Developer

May 2011 — August 2013

BioMed Central, London // www.biomedcentral.com

At BioMed Central online publisher of scientific articles I work as a part of Web Design and User Experience team on designing layouts and front end structure for three main portals and tens of independent journals. I'm also responsible for developing WordPress themes for blogs using responsive web design with HTML5 and CSS3.

Web and Graphic Designer

Aug 2006 — May 2011

Ascent IT Ltd, London // www.hueanimation.com

While working for Ascent IT Ltd online retailer I was responsible for designing and maintaining three main websites (www.hueanimation.com, www.huehd.com and www. sogatel.com) as well as micro pages for single products. I've also created a number of eBay templates with Flash and JavaScript elements as well as email campaigns, banners and other promotional digital material. I was also responsible for designing GUI for Stop Motion Animation software and producing packaging designs which include boxes, user guides, CD artworks with interactive installation screens.

EDUCATION

ABC Level 3 Certificate in Digital Graphics

Sept 2008 — Aug 2009

London College of Communication, Elephant & Castle, London

BSc Computer Science with Business Management Sept 2002 — Jun 2005

The University of Management and Marketing, Sosnowiec, Poland

A-Levels (Polish, Mathematics, Geography)

Sept 1998 — Jun 2002

Electronics and Informatics High School, Sosnowiec, Poland

E: pietraszek@hotmail.co.uk

W: looca.co.uk

L: linkedin.com/in/pietraszekl

T: twitter.com/pietraszekl

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Sass, Less, UX, Responsive Web Design, Web Standards, Usability

TOOLS

Hybris [y] CMS, Wordpress, Eclipse, GIT, SVN, GruntJS, Axure RP, Photoshop, Illustrator

WORK EXAMPLES

www.ab.gr shop.delhaize.be www.poferries.com uk.monsoon.co.uk biomedcentral.com/biome BMC Research Awards beyond-the-genome.com elenabudnikova.com hueanimation.com

CLIENTS

Delhaize Group
Phones4U
Office Shoes
Costco
Monsoon/Accessorize
P&O Ferries
British American Tobacco

66 Lukasz is a great addition to our UI team at Portaltech Reply. He is a 'go-to' person when you need a quick and complete solution. Technical and with a keen eye for detail, Lukasz also has the rare quality of genuine self drive which has displayed itself whilst being UI project lead for one of our largest global clients.
 59
 51

Head of UX at Portaltech Reply